(Sheldon:)Oh. Well, the real surprise is
(Sheldon:)how surprised you are
that I'm great at surprises.
(Amy:)Well, that's not a
surprise at all.
(Amy:)I mean, if I knew you
were good at surprises,
(Amy:)I would have
expected the surprise,
and therefore not
have been surprised.
But as it is,
I didn't know,
and therefore my surprise
should be unsurprising.
(Sheldon:)Don't get me all randy.
Guests are on the way.
(Leonard:)Hi.
(Bernadette:)Hey, where you been?
(Howard:)Oh, we went and did a little
shopping for the baby.
(Raj:)Wait till you see
the crib we found.
(Bernadette:)You bought a crib without me?
(Howard:)You're gonna love it.
Yeah.
(Raj:)It's the highest rated one
on the market.
(Raj:)I wouldn't even
call it a crib.
(Raj:)I'd call it a Fortress
of Solitude for babies.
(Bernadette:)Sounds expensive.
(Howard:)Okay, well,
I may have gone
(Howard:)a bit overboard, but you can't
put a price on safety.
(Raj:)Though if you did, it's more
zeroes than you're expecting.
(Howard:)But it's the safest crib
you can buy.
(Howard:)And if you don't like it,
we can return it.
(Sheldon:)Fine.
In our new minivan.
(Howard:)Hey, what's for lunch?